Joaquin Palmeyro

Software Developer



PROFILE

Experienced full-stack developer specializing in scalable system and web application development, platform analysis and design, process optimization, documentation development, and team organization. I approach challenges proactively and responsibly, with the ability to adapt and learn in both team and individual environments.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ITPort - Weeot

Software Developer May 2023 - Present

Specialized in system development, my work has been done using full-stack technologies:

React and NodeJS with Express + mysql2, and SQLyog as the database management tool.

In charge of the development and analysis of the platform, process optimization, and repository management in projects such as UOM: Boletas, Padrón Social, Padrón Sindical, and Digital Credential; Boletín Oficial of CABA, and the Administration System for the Juegos Evita 2022.

Tenaris

Remote control crane operator

Logistics in the tubular movement sector at LACO1.

August 2022 - December 2022

EDUCATION

UTN - Facultad Regional Delta

Programming Universitary Technician - Completed

2021 - 2024

Instituto Federico Dickens - Colegio Secundario

Bachelor's Degree in Economics and Business Administration – Completed

2015 - 2020

TECHNICAL BACKGROUND

- ReactJS
- Github Git
- NodeJS
- Draw io
- Express
- VSCode
- MySQL
- Figma

LANGUAGES

SPANISH

Native

ENGLISH

B2